Hi Ga Mitra, how to get bike insurance done with ID, if you
click on two layers then you will
click on OK, after that the two layers option will come, a QR will be generated, take a screenshot of it or take a photo, after taking the photo, open the order, search on lines on chrome and
view it, a link will be generated,
after the link is generated you will enter the mobile number of the
customer,
after entering the customer's mobile number you will
submit, after submitting a window
will open on it the customer's name will be there,
what is the name in the Aadhar card of the vehicle,
after that enter the mobile number, then the mail ID,
then enter the vehicle number, after entering the mobile number, enter the number, after that submit, if it is an email number, enter it,
after submitting, the data will come, the
data of the vehicle will come out,
who bought it, when did
you buy it, after ticking the purchase, you will do
third party insurance, this will be the third
party insurance of this vehicle,
tick on third party, after ticking on third party
it will also come 14, after that if you enter 15 lakhs
then you will get 83 for third party, the
third party will be in 83  We will continue,
after continuing it will be eKYC,
CKYC will do half KYC in CKYC,
now we will enter the Aadhar number of the customer,
Aadhar card number of the owner of the vehicle,
after that we will enter the name
which is to be entered in the half card,
after that we will enter the date of birth of the customer,
like I am selecting the date of
birth of customer
[sangeet] as
1989, we will submit that
Aadhar card
name male female and date of birth, after that we will
submit, if half card number is entered then
OTP will be sent, if I do
not have it then OTP will not be sent, so I
entered the OTP, after that I took the photo of the Aadhar card,
we will upload that front side photo,
after that we will upload the back side photo of the
Aadhar card,
like I am doing, after that we will submit,
submit,
you can see it is
waiting, you will have to wait for some time, it is
in processing, after that the details will come,
after the details come we will submit it,
after doing this our KYC is done,
now after that the details of the vehicle will open, in that
you will see Mr./Mrs. whatever it
is  You will have to tick and
fill in the owner's address. You are
filling only the owner's address
of the vehicle and will enter the pin code.
After the pin code, you will continue.
After checking it once, you will continue.
[Music]
After continuing, you will get the payment
option. You can make payment through UPI, you
can make payment through PhonePe, you can also make payment through QR.
So I will make QR through PhonePe, I will make
payment through PhonePe. I will tick on PhonePe.
After that, PhonePe will open. In it, a
payment option will appear for 843. So I am making payment of 843. I am
entering my password. There is a
PIN. I am entering that.
After entering the PIN, the payment has been done. The payment has been done
successfully. You can see that the
payment has been done successfully. After that,
our B will be completed.
After completion, you
can also download its PDF. The PDF
option is coming below. You can download the PDF. You will
download it and get the print out by downloading the PDF.
[Music] The
PDF will be downloaded and you can also see it.
Okay guys, please subscribe to my channel,
my channel Kamal Tech.  24